do it do it do it
[music]
do it
[music] do it
[music] do it [music] do it
[music]
hello hello friends I am Vishal and you are
watching my channel, it is very good,
through accident claim this car is
ready for acquisition with us, due to some reason we had done
its rebuilding process, we
spent a lot of time on it but could
not make a video of it but I thought that since it is the first time a
TV operator has come,
I should at least give you the information about its parts,
how is the part price, how much is it, so the
parts of this car have not changed much,
if there has been some change in understanding, two-three things, which should be
told to you people, this car
is well, people have dead sales and a
bill of ₹6700 ₹70 has been made, okay, so let's
just see in that, we have half the charge on reducing the price of the part to
half, so we will see
how much we get, I will
not be able to tell you how much claim we get for this car,
whatever bill the company would have sent, you will
know how much tax is being set, Sagar,
you also want to know that  How much is the line
getting for, so I
write it in all the details in the description, the price of the pass, total
bill, everything, how much did I get the plan,
I mention it there, so by asking this question everyone
can see
how much is the price of each tear, how much was the total plan, how much was the total, so
let me tell you right now
which changes were there,
how much is the price of the text, first of all you guys see
this headlight, this Azhar light positive has been
changed, this is its name, your
Yo Yo was robbed of Rs 598, this guy has changed it to us,
friends Madhur Pradhan, and along with that,
this one of your horse
TVS has also been changed, it is of Rs 11 problem
and this one is a different dip, every
part of this sir, this is also changed, it is of Rs 13 100
and this film of yours which was at the back has been changed for
Rs 500,
Shyam and five times when there is a
car accident, for
quiet an alarm inch extra should be taken,
so we are  The agreement that has been made between them is
also linked to it, so it will
keep ₹67 100 away, so let's see
how many kg the customer gets, the
alarms I want to say that we keep making such
accidental claim related refilling related
videos and keep uploading them,
if you like watching such videos
and have come to our channel for the first time, then
subscribe to our channel
so that you can get notifications whenever we upload them
and do subscribe because we really
need your support, please
share it with those who do TVS Radeon, how can the money
reach Adidas, okay with this note,
thank you very much for
taking out your precious time and watching our video,
so thank you very much
subscribe, share, like, Jai Hind,
Kar Do, Kar
Do,
Scientist
[Music], it has happened
[Music], Kar Do, Kar Do [
Music], Kar Do,
Jhal
[Prashant], it has happened
and tell
Ajay to Kar Do, show more Kar
Do,
show more Kar Do,
Ajay to
Kar Do
[Music], it has
happened
[Music]